<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tools on unsigned pixel</title>
    <link>http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/tags/tools/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tools on unsigned pixel</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2016 09:34:49 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/tags/tools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>git rebase wwdc2016</title>
      <link>http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/2016/06/git-rebase-wwdc2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2016 09:34:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/2016/06/git-rebase-wwdc2016/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I couldn&amp;rsquo;t watch all of the WWDC 2016 keynote and caught only the last bits of macOS Sierra and some iMessage stuff. The latter I couldn&amp;rsquo;t really make sense of at the time, but I don&amp;rsquo;t snapchat or use other messengers besides iMessage. So not having watched the whole thing, I was a bit underwhelmed. Nevertheless, a lot of tweets this week showed how many exciting new API there are to explore and I am really looking forward to do so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I picked up a copy of Paul Hudsons &lt;a href=&#34;https://gum.co/beyondcode&#34;&gt;Beyond Code&lt;/a&gt; to get up to speed with &lt;code&gt;git&lt;/code&gt; and terminal and will have to rebase all the WWDC tweets for linear reading&amp;hellip; Pauls books are definitely worth reading. At the moment, they complement my level of experience just right.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>git setup</title>
      <link>http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/2016/05/git-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2016 23:25:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/2016/05/git-setup/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I realized that I definitly have to have version control set up before even thinking about editing the configuration of a mostly unknown system like &lt;a href=&#34;http://gohugo.io&#34;&gt;hugo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I only have working knowledge of subversion, but need to get up too speed with Git anyway, so I had to find a good resource to get into using Git quickly. The &lt;a href=&#34;https://git-scm.com/book&#34;&gt;git book&lt;/a&gt; is very thorough, but too long for a quick start, so I opted for &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.git-tower.com/learn/git/ebook&#34;&gt;Learn Version Control with Git&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>