<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>unsigned pixel</title>
    <link>http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on unsigned pixel</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2016 22:10:50 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>YAFRA</title>
      <link>http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/yafra/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2016 22:10:50 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/yafra/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;None of the film roll apps (think manual EXIF recording for the analog shooter) I looked at met my personal needs. So it is time for YAFRA(yet another film roll app).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>straight camera</title>
      <link>http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/straight-camera/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2016 22:10:24 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/straight-camera/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It will be about straight lines&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>podcast connection</title>
      <link>http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/podcast-connection/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2016 21:09:17 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/podcast-connection/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;nothing but some tests running in XCode to see here yet.
&lt;img src=&#34;http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/blog/images/IMG_1802.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;testing&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>slow progress</title>
      <link>http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/2016/07/slow-progress/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2016 22:04:24 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/2016/07/slow-progress/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Automating the &lt;a href=&#34;http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/2016/05/bootstrapping/&#34;&gt;infrastructure&lt;/a&gt; has been assigned a lower priority once more, because I want to get some serious work on an iOS project done.  The code name for that project is &lt;em&gt;PodcastConnection&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;em&gt;PodcastConnection&lt;/em&gt; will make featured (photography) podcasts more accessible for people that have no idea what a podcast, a podcatcher or even
Apple&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href=&#34;https://itunes.apple.com/en/app/podcasts/id525463029?mt=8&#34;&gt;Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; app is. So why is this post titled &amp;lsquo;slow progress&amp;rsquo;? Coding algorithms or data structures  is quite easy in Swift, but getting to grips with idomatic Cocoa and how to wire together Views and Controllers has been a bit of a struggle for me. But tonight, I could finally see the light at the end of the tunnel, and it was neither a freight train nor a Pokemon Go player with a flashlight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[Update: I intend to open source &lt;em&gt;PodcastConnection&lt;/em&gt; (it is not rocket science anyway), but being the perfectionist I am, I&amp;rsquo;ll keep it in a private &lt;a href=&#34;https://Bitbucket.org&#34;&gt;Bitbucket&lt;/a&gt; repo until I am at least half way satisfied with the code.]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[Another Update: Since &lt;em&gt;PodcastConnection&lt;/em&gt; is going to be a collaboration between me an the guy who actually asked for such an app, it isn&amp;rsquo;t my sole decision to open source it. And considering some points made in episode 37 of &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.relay.fm/radar&#34;&gt;Under the Radar&lt;/a&gt; it might not be the best idea anyway&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>git rebase wwdc2016</title>
      <link>http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/2016/06/git-rebase-wwdc2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2016 09:34:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/2016/06/git-rebase-wwdc2016/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I couldn&amp;rsquo;t watch all of the WWDC 2016 keynote and caught only the last bits of macOS Sierra and some iMessage stuff. The latter I couldn&amp;rsquo;t really make sense of at the time, but I don&amp;rsquo;t snapchat or use other messengers besides iMessage. So not having watched the whole thing, I was a bit underwhelmed. Nevertheless, a lot of tweets this week showed how many exciting new API there are to explore and I am really looking forward to do so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I picked up a copy of Paul Hudsons &lt;a href=&#34;https://gum.co/beyondcode&#34;&gt;Beyond Code&lt;/a&gt; to get up to speed with &lt;code&gt;git&lt;/code&gt; and terminal and will have to rebase all the WWDC tweets for linear reading&amp;hellip; Pauls books are definitely worth reading. At the moment, they complement my level of experience just right.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cheap is expensive</title>
      <link>http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/2016/05/cheap-is-expensive/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2016 23:12:43 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/2016/05/cheap-is-expensive/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The plan was to automate static generation of the site to the point where I just add/edit a post, run a script that builds the site and do an automatic upload.
 Later on, building should be via &lt;a href=&#34;https://jenkins.io/index.html&#34;&gt;Jenkins&lt;/a&gt; or a similar tool. But my cheap hoster gives me no &lt;code&gt;ssh&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code&gt;rsync&lt;/code&gt; access and I spent the better part of the evening trying to figure out how to automate the upload of the files. This was rather expensive in terms of time that I could have better spent programming &amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But then &lt;a href=&#34;https://duck.sh&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;duck&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt; of Cyberduck fame came to the rescue and I am one step closer to automated site generation.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sidetracked</title>
      <link>http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/2016/05/sidetracked/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2016 21:23:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/2016/05/sidetracked/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Instead of setting up a workflow for automating this blog &lt;a href=&#34;http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/2016/05/bootstrapping/&#34;&gt;(see bootstrapping)&lt;/a&gt;, I decided to use a different theme (&lt;em&gt;casper&lt;/em&gt; instead of &lt;em&gt;beautifulhugo&lt;/em&gt;) and lost a bit sight of the original goal, so please bear with me&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>git setup</title>
      <link>http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/2016/05/git-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2016 23:25:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/2016/05/git-setup/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I realized that I definitly have to have version control set up before even thinking about editing the configuration of a mostly unknown system like &lt;a href=&#34;http://gohugo.io&#34;&gt;hugo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I only have working knowledge of subversion, but need to get up too speed with Git anyway, so I had to find a good resource to get into using Git quickly. The &lt;a href=&#34;https://git-scm.com/book&#34;&gt;git book&lt;/a&gt; is very thorough, but too long for a quick start, so I opted for &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.git-tower.com/learn/git/ebook&#34;&gt;Learn Version Control with Git&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>bootstrapping</title>
      <link>http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/2016/05/bootstrapping/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 19:39:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/2016/05/bootstrapping/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After dabbling around for a while with &lt;a href=&#34;http://gohugo.io&#34;&gt;hugo&lt;/a&gt;, I decided to establish a real blogging workflow with that static site generator. And why not blog about, too?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The rough idea is that I&amp;rsquo;ll script site generation first, put the site sources under version control and set up a Jenkins job to publish to my actual site.
One could argue that putting the whole thing up on Github would be much easier, but I have to expand my knowledge on CI anyway and this should be a fun project to do so.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>zalando</title>
      <link>http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/2016/03/zalando/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2016 22:34:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/2016/03/zalando/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Nothing to see here, please move along!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>welcome to unsigned pixel</title>
      <link>http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/2015/09/welcome-to-unsigned-pixel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/2015/09/welcome-to-unsigned-pixel/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A new site for my programming activities. For more info, please refer to the &lt;a href=&#34;http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/about/&#34;&gt;about page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2016 22:34:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Why &lt;strong&gt;unsigned pixel&lt;/strong&gt; ?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wanted a somewhat nerdy name, because this site is related to my software development activities. So I used &lt;code&gt;unsigned&lt;/code&gt; as a reference to programming and &lt;code&gt;pixel&lt;/code&gt; as a reference to digital photography.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Impressum</title>
      <link>http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/impressum/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2015 19:02:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/impressum/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Christian Scheer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Oberschlesierstr. 15&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;44141 Dortmund&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;info at unsignedpixel.com&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Disclaimer – rechtliche Hinweise&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Haftungsbeschränkung Die Inhalte dieser Website werden mit größtmöglicher Sorgfalt erstellt. Der Anbieter übernimmt jedoch keine Gewähr für die Richtigkeit, Vollständigkeit und Aktualität der bereitgestellten Inhalte. Die Nutzung der Inhalte der Website erfolgt auf eigene Gefahr des Nutzers. Namentlich gekennzeichnete Beiträge geben die Meinung des jeweiligen Autors und nicht immer die Meinung des Anbieters wieder. Mit der reinen Nutzung der Website des Anbieters kommt keinerlei Vertragsverhältnis zwischen dem Nutzer und dem Anbieter zustande.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Externe Links Diese Website enthält Verknüpfungen zu Websites Dritter (“externe Links”). Diese Websites unterliegen der Haftung der jeweiligen Betreiber. Der Anbieter hat bei der erstmaligen Verknüpfung der externen Links die fremden Inhalte daraufhin überprüft, ob etwaige Rechtsverstöße bestehen. Zu dem Zeitpunkt waren keine Rechtsverstöße ersichtlich. Der Anbieter hat keinerlei Einfluss auf die aktuelle und zukünftige Gestaltung und auf die Inhalte der verknüpften Seiten. Das Setzen von externen Links bedeutet nicht, dass sich der Anbieter die hinter dem Verweis oder Link liegenden Inhalte zu Eigen macht. Eine ständige Kontrolle dieser externen Links ist für den Anbieter ohne konkrete Hinweise auf Rechtsverstöße nicht zumutbar. Bei Kenntnis von Rechtsverstößen werden jedoch derartige externe Links unverzüglich gelöscht.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Urheber- und Leistungsschutzrechte Die auf dieser Website veröffentlichten Inhalte unterliegen dem deutschen Urheber- und Leistungsschutzrecht. Jede vom deutschen Urheber- und Leistungsschutzrecht nicht zugelassene Verwertung bedarf der vorherigen schriftlichen Zustimmung des Anbieters oder jeweiligen Rechteinhabers. Dies gilt insbesondere für Vervielfältigung, Bearbeitung, Übersetzung, Einspeicherung, Verarbeitung bzw. Wiedergabe von Inhalten in Datenbanken oder anderen elektronischen Medien und Systemen. Inhalte und Rechte Dritter sind dabei als solche gekennzeichnet. Die unerlaubte Vervielfältigung oder Weitergabe einzelner Inhalte oder kompletter Seiten ist nicht gestattet und strafbar. Lediglich die Herstellung von Kopien und Downloads für den persönlichen, privaten und nicht kommerziellen Gebrauch ist erlaubt. Die Darstellung dieser Website in fremden Frames ist nur mit schriftlicher Erlaubnis zulässig.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Datenschutz Durch den Besuch der Website des Anbieters können Informationen über den Zugriff (Datum, Uhrzeit, betrachtete Seite) gespeichert werden. Diese Daten gehören nicht zu den personenbezogenen Daten, sondern sind anonymisiert. Sie werden ausschließlich zu statistischen Zwecken ausgewertet. Eine Weitergabe an Dritte, zu kommerziellen oder nichtkommerziellen Zwecken, findet nicht statt. Der Anbieter weist ausdrücklich darauf hin, dass die Datenübertragung im Internet (z.B. bei der Kommunikation per E-Mail) Sicherheitslücken aufweisen und nicht lückenlos vor dem Zugriff durch Dritte geschützt werden kann. Die Verwendung der Kontaktdaten des Impressums zur gewerblichen Werbung ist ausdrücklich nicht erwünscht, es sei denn der Anbieter hatte zuvor seine schriftliche Einwilligung erteilt oder es besteht bereits eine Geschäftsbeziehung. Der Anbieter und alle auf dieser Website genannten Personen widersprechen hiermit jeder kommerziellen Verwendung und Weitergabe ihrer Daten.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Besondere Nutzungsbedingungen Soweit besondere Bedingungen für einzelne Nutzungen dieser Website von den vorgenannten Nummern 1. bis 4. abweichen, wird an entsprechender Stelle ausdrücklich darauf hingewiesen. In diesem Falle gelten im jeweiligen Einzelfall die besonderen Nutzungsbedingungen. Quelle: Muster-Disclaimer von Juraforum.de in Kooperation mit Experten-Branchenbuch.de&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>