<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ios on unsigned pixel</title>
    <link>http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/tags/ios/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ios on unsigned pixel</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2016 22:10:24 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/tags/ios/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>straight camera</title>
      <link>http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/straight-camera/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2016 22:10:24 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/straight-camera/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It will be about straight lines&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>podcast connection</title>
      <link>http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/podcast-connection/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2016 21:09:17 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/podcast-connection/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;nothing but some tests running in XCode to see here yet.
&lt;img src=&#34;http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/blog/images/IMG_1802.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;testing&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>slow progress</title>
      <link>http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/2016/07/slow-progress/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2016 22:04:24 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/2016/07/slow-progress/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Automating the &lt;a href=&#34;http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/2016/05/bootstrapping/&#34;&gt;infrastructure&lt;/a&gt; has been assigned a lower priority once more, because I want to get some serious work on an iOS project done.  The code name for that project is &lt;em&gt;PodcastConnection&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;em&gt;PodcastConnection&lt;/em&gt; will make featured (photography) podcasts more accessible for people that have no idea what a podcast, a podcatcher or even
Apple&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href=&#34;https://itunes.apple.com/en/app/podcasts/id525463029?mt=8&#34;&gt;Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; app is. So why is this post titled &amp;lsquo;slow progress&amp;rsquo;? Coding algorithms or data structures  is quite easy in Swift, but getting to grips with idomatic Cocoa and how to wire together Views and Controllers has been a bit of a struggle for me. But tonight, I could finally see the light at the end of the tunnel, and it was neither a freight train nor a Pokemon Go player with a flashlight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[Update: I intend to open source &lt;em&gt;PodcastConnection&lt;/em&gt; (it is not rocket science anyway), but being the perfectionist I am, I&amp;rsquo;ll keep it in a private &lt;a href=&#34;https://Bitbucket.org&#34;&gt;Bitbucket&lt;/a&gt; repo until I am at least half way satisfied with the code.]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[Another Update: Since &lt;em&gt;PodcastConnection&lt;/em&gt; is going to be a collaboration between me an the guy who actually asked for such an app, it isn&amp;rsquo;t my sole decision to open source it. And considering some points made in episode 37 of &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.relay.fm/radar&#34;&gt;Under the Radar&lt;/a&gt; it might not be the best idea anyway&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>git rebase wwdc2016</title>
      <link>http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/2016/06/git-rebase-wwdc2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2016 09:34:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://unsignedpixel.com/blog/2016/06/git-rebase-wwdc2016/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I couldn&amp;rsquo;t watch all of the WWDC 2016 keynote and caught only the last bits of macOS Sierra and some iMessage stuff. The latter I couldn&amp;rsquo;t really make sense of at the time, but I don&amp;rsquo;t snapchat or use other messengers besides iMessage. So not having watched the whole thing, I was a bit underwhelmed. Nevertheless, a lot of tweets this week showed how many exciting new API there are to explore and I am really looking forward to do so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I picked up a copy of Paul Hudsons &lt;a href=&#34;https://gum.co/beyondcode&#34;&gt;Beyond Code&lt;/a&gt; to get up to speed with &lt;code&gt;git&lt;/code&gt; and terminal and will have to rebase all the WWDC tweets for linear reading&amp;hellip; Pauls books are definitely worth reading. At the moment, they complement my level of experience just right.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>